Mukhammadzhon Khakimov

Frontend Developer

Last update: December 6, 2022

Up-to-date version of CV is available at

1 https://Muhammadzhon.github.io/muhammad-bio

Residence	♠ Osh, Kyrgyzstan
Linkedin	Mukhammadzhon
GitHub	Muhammadzhon
Phone	+996 (555) 00 43 45
Email	<u> hmuhammadjon</u>

HTML CSS SPA Github JavaScript React English Turkish Russian

I'm a frontend developer. The purpose of my last 5 years happened to find the job which I love. And I realized only web development was going to fill my path of life! Studied HTML, CSS and JavaScript, now I'm learning React and It makes me confident and ambitious.

Professional Experience

10/2022 - Current

Intern

Bi-Soft Ltd takes leading position in Kyrgyzstan market.

As a Trainee my task is:

- * Analyze the code structure
- * Maintain software specifications
- * Work closely with other developers
- * Accomplish tasks which was given by teamlead
- * Write clear and consistent code

Good knowledge of HTML5, CSS3, Javascript and Git Strong communication skills Well organized team player

11/2022 - present

Way of Samurai project

Way of Samurai is a replica of social media paltform

As a lerner I'm:

- * Studying framework React
- * Practicing HTML, CSS and JS
- * Writing code on VS Code editor
- * Learning to devide into components
- * Rebuilding the project from scratches

Education

Ahmet Yesevi International Kazak-Turkish University [2011 - 2016]